Roll call.
Mr. Miller. Here. Mr. Behram. Here. Ms. Heckman. Here. Mr. Ford.
Mr. Ford is excused. Mr. Wallace. Here. Mr. Davis. Here.
Hear item 2. Invocation pledge of allegiance.
The invocation of this evening will be given by Imam Rashad Khalifa of the Islamic mosque of Tucson.
Will you please remain standing for the pledge of allegiance to the flag?
In the name of God, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
Praise be to God, Lord of the universe.
The Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
Master of the Day of Recompense.
Only You we worship. Only You we ask for help.
Guide us in the right path.
The path of those who deserve Your blessings.
Not of those who incurred Your displeasure
Nor of those who go astray.
Amen.